# **OMID REYHANI**

SENIOR SOFTWARE ENGINEER AT INTERNATIONAL ATOMIC ENERGY AGENCY (IAEA)

#### **ABOUT**

AUSTRIA

OMID.REYHANI@GMAIL.COM

☑\*

+43(660)2279747 **3** 

in IN/REYHANI ♂

#### SOFTWARE ENGINEER

#### MASTER

NODEJS
JAVASCRIPT
TYPESCRIPT
HTML 5
CSS
SASS
ANGULAR
REACT
VUE.JS
NGRX
RXJS

#### BACKEND

#### **MASTER**

D3.JS

.NET CORE

ASP.NET

ENTITY FRAMEWORK MICROSERVICES

SQL

RABBITMQ

#### **EVERYTHING ELSE**

#### **MASTER**

SDLC TDD CI/CD AGILE SCRUM GIT DOCKER KUBERNETES

#### LANGUAGES

#### **SUMMARY**

Hands-on experience with Angular and React and other frontend frameworks. 14 years of experience writing large complex web-based enterprise applications with .NET (with c#) Ability to track and resolve issues with minimal supervision Nodejs, JavaScript, TypeScript, HTML 5, CSS, SASS, Angular, React, Vue.js, NgRX, RxJS, d3.js, .NET, .NET core, C#, ASP.NET, Entity Framework, Microservices, SQL, RabbitMQ, SDLC, TDD, CI/CD, Agile, Scrum, Git, Docker, kubernetes

#### **EXPERIENCE**

# INTERNATIONAL ATOMIC ENERGY AGENCY (IAEA)

07/2016 - 01/2021

#### SENIOR SOFTWARE ENGINEER

Developing, enhancing secure applications (Angular, ASP.NET), providing an easy interface for states and regional authorities to foster the exchange of scientific and technical information. data access, report, business intelligence, and ... Integration with other internal systems Responsible for bootstrapping both client and serverside of the applications Unit testing, integration and e2e testing CI using TFS build server and InRelease Technologies and Tools: Angular, Typescript, ASP.NET, .NET, C#, JavaScript, SQL, Entity Framework, .Net Core, NodeJs, Bootstrap, Sass, Git, Docker, TDD, Bootstrap, CQRS, Event Sourcing, RabbitMQ

#### EPAM SYSTEMS <sup>☑</sup>

04/2015 - 07/2016

SENIOR ENGINEER

Project: Development of a Calculation Engine for an insurance company Tasks: Developing web services using WCF Solely responsible for developing frontend UI with angularjs and .net web api Designing and developing databases Deployment and maintenance of software products CI using TFS build server and Octopus Implementing unit and integration tests Daily meeting with customers from the USA Technologies and Tools: TFS, Microsoft SQL Server, .NET, WCF, C#, AngularJs

## 

12/2014 - 04/2015

SENIOR SOFTWARE ENGINEER

Project: Development for irr.ru website Tasks and Accomplishments: Performed technical analysis of latest technologies Provided basic guidelines for E2E and unit testing Implemented business requirements using JavaScript Technologies and Tools: MySQL, WebStorm, JIRA, Grunt, NodeJs, AngularJS, ExtJs, LESS, Twitter Bootstrap

#### TOP SOFT <sup>™</sup>

09/2012 - 11/2013

SENIOR SOFTWARE ENGINEER

Project: HTML5 Applications for Tablets (jQuery mobile) Tasks and Accomplishments: Developed services using WCF Built an interface for generating MDX queries to OLAP databases Optimized WCF service Technologies and Tools: SQL Server, MS SQL Analysis Services, jQuery, d3js, ExtJs OLAP, MDX, SSAS .NET, C#, WCF

#### **NOOR ETISAL**

05/2011 - 05/2012

KEY SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

Project: Business Evaluation Software and Project Management Tasks and Accomplishments: Developed application logic using C# Was responsible for designing and coding Performed unit testing Technologies and Tools: Microsoft SQL Server, .NET, WPF, ASP.NET, C#

# KHOBRE PARDAZ PARS CO.LTD ☑

03/2010 - 05/2011

KEY SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

Project: Bank lottery application Tasks and Accomplishments: Was responsible for requirement gathering for product design and application development Implemented business logic inside stored procedures, inside c# application Performed extensive

ENGLISH (FLUENT) RUSSIAN (FLUENT) FRENCH (BASIC) database programming (sync data with bank, lottery algorithms implementations) Was engaged in designing reports using Crystal Report Designed a completely new interface for existing ERP application / Silverlight whiteboard & image editor Technologies and Tools: Microsoft SQL Server, DB2, Microsoft SQL Integration Services, WPF, WCF, Silverlight, ADO.NET SQL, Crystal Reports

#### **PARTIAN**

01/2009 - 03/2010

DEVELOPER

Project: Full JavaScript-based client framework (ZINO) including features like XML markup, client-side proxy builder for web services, UI controls. Office automation software (Dario) embracing SOA architecture and exploiting WCF using the ZINO framework Tasks and Accomplishments: Performed both frontend and backend development of the project Developed a proxy builder for WCF services for client applications Technologies and Tools: Microsoft SQL Server, Microsoft BizTalk, .NET, c#, BPMN, Workflow, JavaScript

# NEXT2FRIENDS.COM <sup>☑</sup>

11/2007 - 07/2008

DEVELOPER

Project: Advanced social networking platform tailored for mobile devices and streaming real-time video from the mobile to the web Tasks and Accomplishments: Designed and developed a complex n-tier web application Designed and implemented database entities (tables, stored procedures) Utilized multiple design and architectural patterns Technologies and Tools: Microsoft SQL Server, VSS, .NET, C#, ASP.NET, SQL

#### **EDUCATION**

#### BELARUSIAN NATIONAL TECHNICAL UNIVERSITY

12/2007 - 12/2008

MASTER OF SCIENCE IN ENGINEERING INFORMATION TECHNOLOGIES AND SYSTEMS

### **BELARUSIAN NATIONAL TECHNICAL UNIVERSITY**

12/2002 - 12/2007

BACHELOR OF SCIENCE IN ENGINEERING SOFTWARE OF INFORMATION TECHNOLOGIES